Bhaskar Reddy.K

SR VFX ARTIST

■ Bhaskarvfx10@gmail.com
□ 9867526024
♀ India in https://www.linkedin.com/in/bhaskarreddy10/

SUMMARY

Dynamic and passionate Visual Effects Artist experienced with television and studio feature film schedules. Currently working as a senior compositor at Legend Vfx, Pune,India.I am self-motivated can work well under pressure to meet challenging and critical deadlines,and also implements strong attention to detail and dedication to succeed while developing elements,components and effects for various projects.

EXPERIENCE

Sr.Compositor

LEGEND VFX, PUNE Dec 2019 - Present

After we collided

Sr.Compositor

MONTAGE COLOR VFX, CHINA Nov 2017 - Nov 2019

觉醒年代,奔腾年代,末代厨娘,大宋宫词,河神2,凤唳九天,人鱼传说,攀登者,龙虎山张天师,大圣无双,年兽

Compositor

DOUBLE NEGATIVE, MUMBAI May 2016 - Oct 2017

Fast and Furious 8, Baby Driver, Assassin's Creed, A Cure for Wellness, Star Trek (Beyond).

Compositor

PRIME FOCUS, MUMBAI Sep 2013 - Apr 2016

Paranormal Activity The Ghost Dimension, Sin City: A Dame to kill for, Chronicles. of. the. Ghostly. Tribe, Non Stop, Brothers, Bang Bang, Mary kom, Action Junction

Compositor

REDCHILLIES VFX, MUMBAI Dec 2012 - Sep 2013

Krish 3, Chenni Express

Compositor

PIXION VFX, MUMBAI Jan 2011 - Nov 2012

Transformers-3 (Stereo Paint Artist), Pirates of the Caribbean(Stereo Paint Artist), Singham (compositor), Aarakshan (compositor), Agnepath(Prep/compositor), Delhi Belly (compositor), Force (compositor), Don-2 (Prep/compositor), Tell Me O Kkhuda (compositor), Double Dhamal (compositor), Love Breakup Zindagi (compositor), Talash (compositor), Thank you (Prep/compositor), Aazaan (compositor)

Sterio Paint Artist

PRASAD EFX, CHENNAI Jun 2010 - Dec 2010

Hood Winked-2 (stereo paint), Immortals (stereo paint)

Jr.Compositor

ARS FRAMES Pvt.Ltd, HYDERABAD Apr 2007 - Feb 2010

Gopi Gopika Godhavari (prep/compositor), Mallepuvvu (roto/prep), Kuberulu (roto/paint), Dammunnodu (roto/paint), Mysamma IPS (roto/paint), Raksha (roto/prep), Sashirekha Parinayam (roto/paint), Chedugudu (roto/paint), Srusti-serial (compositor), Sri Venkateswara Mahathyam (compositor).

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Nuke	Premier	
Nuke	FIEITHEI	
Houdini	Blender	
Python	C4D	
Adobe Photoshop		

SKILLS

- Greensreen, Bluescreen and RGB mate extraction
- Multipass CGI Photorealistic Integration
- Experience creating high quality fluid dynamic systems
- · Color correction & Grading
- 3D Compositing
- Houdini FX knowledge
- knowledge of particle systems
- Able to work in a team and under pressure
- · Skilled eye on details
- Ability to adapt quickly to new technologies and applications

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer science (B.Sc(M.P.CS)) National Degree College, Nandyal, A.P, INDIA.

Full Time Animation Program Image Animation Training Institute, Chennai, TN.

HOBBIES

Reading Books Photography

Playing Vedio Games Music

Movies & TV Shows

LANGUAGES